<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Lumen</string>
    <string name="skip">Skip</string>
    <string name="title_activity_consumption">Consumption</string>
    <string name="consumption_tab1">Day</string>
    <string name="consumption_tab2">Month</string>
    <string name="consumption_tab3">Year</string>
    <string name="consumo">Consumption</string>
    <string name="produccion">Production</string>
    <string name="title_activity_production">Production</string>
    <string name="infoSlideString1">Are you aware of how the Spanish energy system works?</string>
    <string name="infoSlideString2">There are four parts that are crucial for this system to function: Generation, transport, distribution and commercialisation.</string>
    <string name="infoSlideString3">The public company in charge of energy transportation is called "Red Electrica de España (REE)". The generation and distribution
        are handled by the spanish energy oligopoly.</string>
    <string name="infoSlideString4">These three companies that generate energy pour it into the grid. REE owns and maintains the grid so the distribution can be done.
        The distributors use this infrastructure so energy can reach the customers through the marketers.</string>
    <string name="infoSlideString5">The daily energy market is called the pool, and It is the place where the marketers (most of them belong to the three big producers)
        buy energy from the producers estimating how much energy is needed at each hour of the day.</string>
    <string name="infoSlideString6">The energy market works in a marginalist way. This way of commercialisation endorses efficient and greener generation techniques. At the moment, this system
        turns to be quite profitable for the producers, because the customers pay each one of the kilowatts they buy at the higher cost (the cassation cost), which is
        fixed by the three oligopolistic companies that run the spanish grid.</string>
</resources>